http://www.ampagency.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
AMP Agency has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to the privacy of visitors to our site. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for ampagency.com and any other website through which we conduct business.
A Special Note About Children
Children under the age of 18 are not eligible to use our services, and we ask that such persons not submit personal information to us. We believe that it's important that parents supervise their children when they are online. As a result, we require that children under the age of 18 use this service only under the direct supervision of parents or guardians.
Information We Collect and Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information
We collect your IP address that could be used to help diagnose problems with our server. Your IP address could also be used to gather broad demographic information and for marketing, and to improve our marketing and measurement systems in order to enhance the user experience.
We use cookies on our site for the purposes of site navigation and for advertising. Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site. Most cookies are "session cookies" which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session. We also use remarketing cookies that can exist up to 90 days after visiting our website. A cookie itself does not have the ability to automatically collect personal information about you. A cookie can store certain information that identifies your computer to us so that you don't have to re-enter information as frequently when you use our site. If you would prefer not to receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to refuse cookies. If you choose to do so, you should understand that some areas of our site will not function properly when you view them. Once you reconfigure your browser to refuse cookies, no additional information will be collected from you or about you through the use of cookies.
In the course of site operation, information collected may be stored and processed in the United States. AMP Agency may collect, hold, and use, directly or through its affiliates, contractors, successors, assigns, and agents, the personally identifiable information collected through the site to present relevant content to a user for both marketing and informational value.
Our site's optional "Contact Us" Request For Information page asks users to give us contact information including your name, email address and phone number (information about age, gender and income will be optional). Contact information is used to contact you to provide more information about AMP Agency and its services by means of our periodic newsletter. Such email messages will provide you with an "opt out" option, which you can use to request not to receive further emails.
Our site's employment opportunity page, includes a submission form on which you may be asked to provide your full name, title, company name, email address, telephone number, how you heard about AMP Agency, the position in which you are interested, and to provide a copy of your resume.
We also occasionally send email to our users announcing special promotions and changes in our services, and other information that we believe will be of interest to our users. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings - see the choice/opt-out section below. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information may be shared with advertisers and our partners only on an aggregate basis, meaning that your personally identifying information is not shared.
If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you. We use information in the file that we maintain for you, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use agreement.
We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability.
Linked Sites
For your convenience, this site contains links to other sites. AMP Agency is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.
Security
This site has industry standard security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All user information stored on our server is stored in an encrypted format.  Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that “perfect security” does not exist on the internet.
Choice/Opt-Out
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to registration@ampagency.com
Change your mailing preferences at http://content.ampagency.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple
Correct/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.
Visit http://content.ampagency.com/hs/manage-preferences/unsubscribe-simple
Contacting AMP Agency
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:
AMP Agency
77 North Washington Street8th FloorBoston, MA 02114
P (617) 837-8200 F (310) 551-0022
You're good to go.
The right person has your information and will get back to you as soon as possible.
Until then...
Read our Behavior Blog
Hello!
My Name is
I'm the
here at
Email me @
and/or call me @
Tell us a little more why you came by today:
Hire AMPWork at AMPJust Saying Hi
What are you looking to accomplish with AMP?
Become Digitally-LedImprove ConversionLaunch a Product/ServiceEnable E-CommerceTransform Into a Product/ServiceBuild LoyaltyCreate Awareness & ConsiderationCultivate CommunityReach New AudiencesActive InfluencersGenerate LeadsBetter Leverage Digital Channels
I heard about AMP from:
User Message
Msg
Next
